[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I hate you!
You ruined my family!
(In Korean)
Enough! Brenda, enough!
Enough!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I apologize for my daughter.
I'm sorry, Hannah.
[MUSIC BECOMES SOFT]
Stop! Both of you!
This time,
you went too far!
You must be accountable
for tampering with documents.
No!
I have to teach you both
a lesson.
Take them to the police!
- [SELENA] (In Korean) No...
- Do it!
Dad, please!
Dad!
- [SELANA SCREAMING IN ANGER]
- [BRENDA CRYING]
Dad, please!
Don't do this!
[SELENA] Min-jae!
Not your daughter!
You should've punished me,
not Hannah.
She has done nothing wrong.
And she deserves to be
part of our family.
Let me go!
[GRUNTS]
[MUSIC BUILDS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Punish me instead.
Just please let my mom
go back to Korea.
Please.
I'm begging you.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
I'm begging you, please!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]